import {
  CHECK_RESPONSE,
  LOGGED_IN,
  SAVE_COOKIE,
  LOG_OUT
} from './actions';

import cookie from 'react-cookie'

export const initialState = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Wermo",
      answer: "A stupid person",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Ee chee wa maa!",
      answer: "Gee whiz",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Kna Naa",
      answer: "Spirit tree",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Jeerota",
      answer: "Friend",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Kreeth",
      answer: "Cave",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Mookiee",
      answer: "Female baby Ewok",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Nuv",
      answer: "Love",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Ooba",
      answer: "Sweet",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Powa",
      answer: "Power",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Roda",
      answer: "To eat",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Sheeu",
      answer: "Name",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Shetai",
      answer: "Warrior",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Sku",
      answer: "Hello",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Sleesh",
      answer: "Berry",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Sunee",
      answer: "Sun",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Teeha",
      answer: "Thank you",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Teeket",
      answer: "Heart",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Sut",
      answer: "Soon",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Thek",
      answer: "Here",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Thees",
      answer: "Good",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "T'hesh",
      answer: "Quiet",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Thuk",
      answer: "Rock",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Treek",
      answer: "Go",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Treekthin",
      answer: "Hourney",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Tu",
      answer: "The",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Weewa",
      answer: "House",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Yeha",
      answer: "Goodbye",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Yehan",
      answer: "Peace",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Yesh",
      answer: "Correct",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Drin",
      answer: "Sick",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Churi",
      answer: "Mountain",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Dutak",
      answer: "Arrow",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Eleeo",
      answer: "Never",
      mValue: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Ehda",
      answer: "Evil",
      mValue: 1
    }
  ],
  responses: [
    // {1, TRUE}
  ],
  numCorrect: 0,
  isLoggedIn: (cookie.load('accessToken') != null)
}

export const Reducer = function(state=initialState, action={}) {
console.log('cookie::::', cookie.load('accessToken'))
  switch(action.type) {

    case CHECK_RESPONSE:
      let questions;
      let numCorrect = state.numCorrect;
      let multiplier = 2;
      let oldQuestion = {...state.questions[0]};
      if (action.isCorrect) {
        multiplier = 3;
        numCorrect++;
      }
      oldQuestion.mValue = oldQuestion.mValue * multiplier;
      questions = state.questions.slice(1, oldQuestion.mValue +  1);
      questions = questions.concat(oldQuestion, state.questions
        .slice(oldQuestion.mValue + 1, state.questions.length));

      return { ...state, questions: questions, 
              numCorrect: numCorrect }

    case LOGGED_IN:
      return {...state, isLoggedIn: true}
    
    case SAVE_COOKIE:
      console.log('save cookie::::', cookie.load('accessToken'))
      return {...state, isLoggedIn: cookie.load('accessToken') != null}

    case LOG_OUT:
      cookie.remove('accessToken')
      return {...state, isLoggedIn: false}
    
    default:
      return state;
  }

}
